cssjockey.com 2016-10-17

# Privacy Policy – CSSJockey.com

The surveillance and confidentiality of our visitors and the registered members is our utmost priority and is promised to NEVER be compromised via any channel. All of your personal information, such as your name, e-mail address, or website information is well protected by our privacy policy. If you come across any breach due to our website, please raise your concern with us immediately at admin[@]cssjockey dot com

By using this site, you agree to the terms of our privacy policy for the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information for the purposes set out below. We do not collect, use or disclose your personal information for any purpose other than those identified below, except with your consent or as required by law.

Information we gather or track:

**Site Activity Data**  
Each time a visitor comes to this website our web server collects and logs certain information. These access logs are kept for a reasonable period of time. These logs include, but are not restricted to your machine’s TCP/IP address, your username (if applicable), date, time and files accessed. These logs also contain information about ‘referrer’ information if you clicked on an external link to a CSSJockey webpage. These logs are used solely for performance, site administration and security reviews. They are not sold or shared in any way to third party organizations.

**Cookies**  
Your browser offers “cookies” which — if you allow their use — store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to our site. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our offerings you like best. And when we make this function available in the future, cookies will enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. However, cookies tell us nothing about you personally unless you specifically give us additional information. This information is used solely to maintain your computer’s session to CSSJockey server. This information is not shared or sold to third party organizations for any purpose.  
Cookies in and of themselves do not contain any personally identifiable information about you.

**Personal Information**  
Personal information, such as your name, email address, or website information is collected only when you voluntarily provide it. Such information is received when you send an email through the site or make some other specific contact, such as completing an online form.

### Non-Disclosure Agreement (NDA) for our Clients

We believe that your personal information including your name, e-mail address, and project related assets belong to you and we do not rent or sell it to third parties. All information provided by you will be used only to process orders.

We respect your work and will only use it to assist you to achieve your goals and your copyrights will remain intact. Any information you share with us, including designs, code, contact information, and client notes will remain confidential and in any case we will not contact your clients or clients of your clients.

### Got Questions?

Feel free to [CONTACT US](http://cssjockey.com/contact "Contact Us") for any further assistance.

Content, Graphics, Themes and Files by [CSSJockey](http://cssjockey.com/) are licensed under a [Creative Commons Attribution-Noncommercial-No Derivative Works 2.5 India License](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/2.5/in/). Based on a work at [www.cssjockey.com](http://cssjockey.com/). Permissions beyond the scope of this license may be available at <http://cssjockey.com/get-in-touch>.

**UPDATED: 26th April, 2013**
